A Guide to the Herman Lemuer Pritchard Papers, 1968-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Herman Lemuer Pritchard Papers, 1968-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1990-048
0.6 cu. ft. 2 boxes
The collection contains papers, photographs, and alumni materials from the VPI Class of 1924 and Associate Director of the Alumni Association from 1967 to 1974, Herman Lemuer Pritchard.
Herman, Lemuer Pritchard
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The collection donated to Special Collections before 1990.
Biographical Note
Herman Lemuer "Lem" Pritchard, born in Norfolk, VA, graduated from VPI in 1924. Following his graduation, Lem went on to become the Vice President of the First Federal Savings and Loan in Patterson, New Jersey. After his retirement, Lem returned to Virginia and was appointed as Associate Alumni Director on June 15, 1967. In November 1967, Pritchard married Clarice Slusher (1904-2005), registrar in the early Hahn administration at Virginia Tech.
Scope and Content
The collection contains materials from the VPI Class of 1924 and Associate Director of the Alumni Association from 1967 to 1974, Herman Lemuer Pritchard. It includes memoranda, images, and correspondence regarding the Alumni Association and its fundraisers and reunions. The collection also contains materials concerning the "Old Guard."
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by material type/subject.
Index Terms
Persons:
Herman, Lemuer Pritchard
Subjects:
University Archives; Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Contents List
- A-C
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Alumni Association Donations (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Alumni (Out-of-Town) (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Alumni Reunion, Class of 1924 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Charter Field Trips (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Class of 1924 (Box-folder 1-8)
  - Corps of Cadets (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Correspondence, 1948-1972 (Box-folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 1-11)
- D-R
  - Delaware Chapter (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Hall, Thomas H. (Alumni Affairs Consultant) (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Homecoming (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Old Guard (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Photographs (Box-folder 2-6)
  - New York City Alumni (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Reunions, 1969 (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Reunion Handbooks: Class and Chapter (Box-folder 2-9)